

KEVIN **AU TAM**

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Passionate coder from Costa Rica, 3 years experience coding with Javascript and React. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. Now learning RUST programming language.

CONTACT ME

Phone

(+506) 7013 1267

Email

kevin.developer71@gmail.com

Github

https://github.com/kevin-dev71

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/kevin-autam/

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Marcadores 247, React Tech Lead and Developer.

at Diurvan Consultores, Apr 2022 - Present, Lima, Perú.

Livescore and results service, stats, live odds and scores from all global matches of different sports. Build with React Nextjs and Nodejs.

Dev: https://dev.tumarcador247.com/ Prod: https://www.marcadores247.com

React Lead Frontend Dev

at Aiko.io (NSFW), Sep 2021 - Apr 2022, Tenerife, Spain. Aiko.io is a NSFW NFT, descentralized marketplace and staking project based on solana blockchain.

- Effectively coded software changes and alterations based on specific design specifications.
- Defining the architecture and the development process of multiple web sites with Nextjs and React.
- Implement UI/UX with React, NextJS, Typescript.
- Implement Solana/web3.js and Smart Contracts Js Binding.

Web Developer as Freelancer

at Freelance Feb 2020- Present, San Jose, Costa Rica. Fullstack small projects as freelancer.

- Frontend Developer, we made the "Tutti-frutti/Stop" game with React, Typescript, Firebase Realtime. https://github.com/frontendcafe/cmykstrawberry
- @diurvanconsultores.com as React developer, i developed custom UI Components with vtex io platform, and coded data adapters to consume vtex middleware service for tiendaclaro peru cl;ient. https://tiendaclaro.pe/.
- · Personal websites.

EDUCATION

Advanced Web Development Bootcamp

at Rooftop Academy, Sep 2021 - Feb, 2022, Cordoba Argentina.

Intern at Rooftop Academy, a complete bootcamp running with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, React, Next JS, React Testing, Git, GitHub, working as Frontend Developer building an Ecommerce Project like Mercadolibre.

Universidad Jose Antonio Paez

Ingeniero en Computación, CS Engineer.

Feb. 2008 - Jan 2013, Valencia, Venezuela.

SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- React
- Git & Github
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Nextjs
- solana/web3.js
- jQuery
- Node.js
- MongoDB
- MySQL, PostgreSQL
- GraphQL, Apollo.
- · Vercel, Heroku, Firebase.
- Collaboration & Teamwork
- React Testing Library Critical Thinking and problem solving.